<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Computer Vision on Life as a young engineer</title><link>https://arthurzucker.github.io/tags/computer-vision/</link><description>Recent content in Computer Vision on Life as a young engineer</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><copyright>Copyright © 2021, Zucker Arthur; all rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 10:12:14 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://arthurzucker.github.io/tags/computer-vision/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Automatic Table Structure Recogniton</title><link>https://arthurzucker.github.io/automatic-table-structure-recogniton/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 10:12:14 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://arthurzucker.github.io/automatic-table-structure-recogniton/</guid><description>During my 3rd yearh internship at Chainos Solution, my collegue Younes Belkda and I developped an automatic Table structure recogniton based on Artificial intelligence. We called it CLUSTI!
Problem statement Some organizations still use huge amounts of scanned tables / invoices. Rather than manually typing the contents of the tables into an excel file, one can think of using Deep Learning to tackle this problem. Once you identify the distinguishable cells on the tables, we can pass an OCR (Optical Character Recognition) to each cell to read its contents and convert it to an excel file for example.</description></item><item><title>BRATS2021, Brain Tumor Segmentation</title><link>https://arthurzucker.github.io/posts/ai-projects/kaggle/brats/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arthurzucker.github.io/posts/ai-projects/kaggle/brats/</guid><description>BRATS (BRAin Tumor Segmentation) is a kaggle competition held every year, which relies on the participation of teams to solve mostly semantic segmentation task related to medical image analysis. This year, the goal of the challenge was to determine the presence of a specific genetic sequence, MGMT promoter methylation, in a tumor, using MRI (Magnetic Resonance Image). This gene sequence plays a strong role in the outcome of chemotherapy in patients with brain tumor, but it can only be analysed using DNA extraction, which takes a lot of time.</description></item></channel></rss>