<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Life as a young engineer</title><link>https://arthurzucker.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Life as a young engineer</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><copyright>Copyright © 2021, Zucker Arthur; all rights reserved.</copyright><atom:link href="https://arthurzucker.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hand Gesture recognition</title><link>https://arthurzucker.github.io/projects/polytech_projects/hand-gesture/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arthurzucker.github.io/projects/polytech_projects/hand-gesture/</guid><description>I will present the Projects I was part of during my engineering school, the different skills required, knowledge etc</description></item><item><title>The Rykyu Flying Foxes</title><link>https://arthurzucker.github.io/projects/flying_foxes/introduction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arthurzucker.github.io/projects/flying_foxes/introduction/</guid><description>Picture of a flying foxe spreading its wings, credits to unsplash
Pteropus dasymallus or Ryukyu Flying Foxes comes from the Pteropodidae family, and belongs to the species of megabats.</description></item><item><title>About me</title><link>https://arthurzucker.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 10:12:14 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://arthurzucker.github.io/about/</guid><description>#my-photo { width: 16rem; margin:0; padding: 0rem; margin: 1rem 1rem 0.5rem 0rem; border-radius: 50%; clear: both; } @media screen and (min-width: 400px) { #my-photo { float: left; } } Hello! I'm Arthur Zucker - I recently graduated from Sorbonne University's Applied Mathematics and computer science engineering school (Polyetch Sorbonne University), and I am currently enrolled at the ENS Paris-Saclay, at the MVA (Mathematics, Vision et Apprentissage) master's degree.</description></item><item><title>[MVA] RL : Reinforcement Learning, how to model an RL problem: Markov Decision Processes</title><link>https://arthurzucker.github.io/notes/rl/lecture1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arthurzucker.github.io/notes/rl/lecture1/</guid><description>r { color: Red } o { color: Orange } g { color: Green } b { color: Blue } The course is provided by Matteo Pirotta a Facebook AI Researcher, and is based on one of the previous MVA RL classes by Alessandro Lazaric (FAIR). @TODO add links to their linkdin or websites
Introduction What is RL? When to use it? Why RL? RL, a short for Reinforcement Learning, is a subclass of machine learning, which focuses on building a model able to learn from his action in an environnement.</description></item><item><title>Automatic Table Structure Recogniton</title><link>https://arthurzucker.github.io/automatic-table-structure-recogniton/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 10:12:14 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://arthurzucker.github.io/automatic-table-structure-recogniton/</guid><description>During my 3rd yearh internship at Chainos Solution, my collegue Younes Belkda and I developped an automatic Table structure recogniton based on Artificial intelligence. We called it CLUSTI!
Problem statement Some organizations still use huge amounts of scanned tables / invoices. Rather than manually typing the contents of the tables into an excel file, one can think of using Deep Learning to tackle this problem. Once you identify the distinguishable cells on the tables, we can pass an OCR (Optical Character Recognition) to each cell to read its contents and convert it to an excel file for example.</description></item><item><title>BRATS2021</title><link>https://arthurzucker.github.io/posts/ai-projects/brats/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arthurzucker.github.io/posts/ai-projects/brats/</guid><description>Recently I am working on BRATS2021 with my long time collegue Younes Belkada.
d2 or (2) AC d2 and BC</description></item><item><title>Local Search Engine</title><link>https://arthurzucker.github.io/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arthurzucker.github.io/search/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>